These inspired performances commanded our attention.
Aceste interpretări spectaculoase ne-au atras atenția.
Drawing us in scene after incredible scene.
Atragându-ne scenă după scenă.
Here are the nominees for best perfomance by an actor in a television series drama
Iată nominalizații la cea mai bună interpretare a unui actor într-o serie de televiziune.
Jason Bateman - Ozark.
Jason Bateman - Ozark.
Josh O'Connor - The Crown
Josh O'Connor - The Crown
Bob Odenkirk - Better Call Saul
Bob Odenkirk - Better Call Saul
Al Pacino - Hunters
Al Pacino - Hunters
Matthew Rhys - Perry Mason
Matthew Rhys - Perry Mason
And the Golden Globe goes to...
Iar Globul de Aur merge la...
Josh O'Connor - The Crown
Josh O'Connor The Crown
Hello everyone!
Salutări tuturor!
Wow, that's quite a surprise, thank you so much!
Uau, asta este o surpriză, vă mulțumesc foarte mult!
Thank you so much to everyone who makes
Mulțumesc nespus de mult tuturor celor care fac
The Crown what it is.
din The Crown ceea ce este.
I've had the time of my life making this show.
Am trăit experiența vieții mele fiind parte din acest show.
So thank you to everyone at Netflix and all the producers and the directors.
Așadar, mulțumesc tuturor celor de la Netflix și tuturor producătorilor și regizorilor.
To our brilliant writer and creator Peter Morgan.
Briliantului nostru scriitor și creator Peter Morgan
To our incredible cast,
Și pentru distribuția noastră incredibilă,